freetastesgood.com 2018-11-04

# Privacy Policy | Free Tastes Good!

### Privacy Policy

Free Tastes Good believes strongly in keeping your personal information confidential. The following policy describes what information we collect and how it is used and shared.

### Information Collected

Free Tastes Good collects as little information as possible from users looking to post comments and messages. We will typically collect a name, personal website, and e-mail address. This helps so we know you are not a robot 🙂 

### Cookies / IP Address tracking

Free Tastes Good uses cookies to uniquely identify users for the purpose of log files and posting comments. No personal information is stored in these cookies and it simply a way to identify your computer.

### With Whom Information is Shared

None of your information will be shared with third parties. Free Tastes Good may use your e-mail address in the future to contact you regarding the site, however, an opt-out will always be provided at bottom of email.  Your name and website may be displayed on the site if you post a comment. However, your e-mail address and privacy will always be kept secure.

### Opting Out

Free Tastes Good sends out daily newsletters, if you sign up.  However, at the bottom of every newsletter will be an easy way to opt-out should you choose you no longer want to receive the daily newsletter.  We don’t like SPAM as much as you and have no intention of filling up e-mail boxes with unwanted messages.

### Third Party Advertising

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our website. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third-party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org.

This post may contain affiliate links. Read my complete [Disclosure Policy Here](http://www.freetastesgood.com/disclosure-statement)
